Ryan Hull

San Francisco Bay Area



ryandelonhull@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/ryan-hull-94003144

Summary

I just finished up a distance learning coding bootcamp from UC Berkeley and can't wait to get my career off the ground in the tech industry. Currently sharpening my skills with online learning and challenging ideas.

I have experience managing people, setting schedules, working with clients, and enforcing maintenance standards in the retail industry. I have IT experience for a state health department working with health care workers and officials. I also have more experience working with customers in the restaurant industry.

Experience



Fullstack Web Development Bootcamp at Berkeley University

University of California, Berkeley

Sep 2020 - Present (4 months +)

Taking a chance at a career change into the tech industry thanks to covid.

N Maintenance Supervisor

Nordstrom

Aug 2019 - Sep 2020 (1 year 2 months)

Manage the maintenance side of multiple retail stores. Order supplies for the day to day cleaning and maintaining of restrooms, floors, fitting rooms, elevators/escalators, boiler room, alterations, restaurant, etc. Manage cleaning employees and cleaning company for certain stores. Maintain and repair HVAC, boiler, alterations equipment, shelving, etc. Work with contractors for big repairs, maintaining sprinklers, recycling and trash pickup, etc. Work closely with store manager and rest of management team on new projects, maintaining covid cleaning protocols, anything else that can come up.

N Maintenance Specialist

Nordstrom

Jul 2017 - Aug 2019 (2 years 2 months)

Maintained and used HVAC, plumbing, electrical, and cleaning equipment for the store. Changed bulbs, ballasts, exit signs, and lighting fixtures. Cleaned carpets and fixed vacuum cleaners. Maintained store cleanliness and made sure any spills or trouble spots were taken care of. Cleaned out HVAC equipment and changed filters.

N Logistics Specialist

Nordstrom

Dec 2015 - Jun 2017 (1 year 7 months)

Started in logistics for Nordstrom in Chicago getting product ready for the store, making back areas easier to navigate and find product, and working with supervisors and selling staff. Then moved to

Minneapolis and stayed in logistics for a few months then started selling in kids shoes for six months. Then moved to working on the night truck to have more time with my kid in the day.



Apprentice Electrician

International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW)

Aug 2014 - Oct 2015 (1 year 3 months)

Tore down old building framework and built in new electrical system. Put up cans and transformer boxes and ran pipe to new boxes, lighting, switches, and other feeds. Used hand benders, Saws-alls, band saws, cordless drills, hog's heads, hand tools, etc. Pulled wire through pipe and wired up fuse boxes, power boxes, lighting, switches, etc.



Operations Consultant

State of Florida

Dec 2010 - Aug 2014 (3 years 9 months)

Operations Consultant --

System Administrator for the Health Management System for Duval County. Resolve performance and network issues from clinical, billing, front desk, and administrative staff through in house help desk system. Work with staff supervisors on implementation and training new network procedures and modules. Create and maintain reports through Excel, Access, SQL, and Crystal Reports.

Education



Jacksonville University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Sociology

Skills

Microsoft Office • JavaScript • React.js • HTML5 • Research • Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)
REST APIs
Bulma (CSS Framework)
JSON